

ALDI ALFIANDI

(Birth Name: Dang Aldi Haediar Ali Alfiandi Albar)
Full-stack Website Developer, IT Support Role, Coding Educator, Office Administrator
Male | He/Him | 23 y.o. | August 27th, 2000. | Straight/Heterosexual | Married | Sukabumi, West Java, Indonesia.
aldialfiandi2708@gmail.com | +62-851-7444-8002 | https://github.com/lev10sa | https://lev10sa.github.io

PROFILE

SUMMARY

I started my career in 2021 and I have gained experience in full-stack website development, IT support, office administration, and anything related to these fields. I am adaptable to any situation and have a proven record of providing solutions, solving various problems, following instructions, fulfilling client requests, and delivering client satisfaction. I am moderately fluent in both English and Indonesian Languages. I am an initiative-taking learner who thrives on new challenges and purposeful endeavors. I consistently bring loyalty, dignity, integrity, trustworthiness, effort, and dedication to achieving goals. I used to work on website development with PHP Native.

EXPERIENCE

PT. SOLUSI EDUKASI GEMILANG

(Company/Corporate)
March 2023 – Present (Currently Working)
IT Support Role (Remote/WFA)
Salary: Rp. 5.635.350,00 per month

Working hours: max. 40 hours per week and max. 8 hours per day

Supporting sales, purchasing, and digital marketing team on IT related matters

LEV10CODE

(Freelance/Self-Employment)
September 2022 – Present (Currently Working)
Coding Educator (Remote/WFA)
Average earnings: Rp. 1.000.000.00 to Rp. 1.50

Average earnings: Rp. 1,000.000,00 to Rp. 1.500.000,00 per month Working hours: 2 days per week (on weekend) and max. 4 hours per day

• Tutoring about Website Programming from basic to intermediate

LEV10SA

(Freelance/Self-Employment)
August 2021 – Present (Currently Working)
Full-stack Website Developer (Remote/WFA)
Average earnings: Rp. 1.500.000,00 to Rp. 4.000.000,00 per month
Working hours: flexible, deadline based

- Developing a full-stack website with MERN or LAMP Stack
- Project maintenance and troubleshooting

DINAS KOMUNIKASI DAN INFORMATIKA KOTA SUKABUMI

(Government/Agency)
April 2018 – August 2018
Office Administrator Intern (Onsite/WFO)
Working hours: max. 40 hours per week and max. 8 hours per day

Managing office administration related matters

EDUCATION

SMK ISLAM PENGUJI SUKABUMI

(Vocational School) Year of 2016 to 2019 (Graduated) Class of Software Engineer

EXPERTISE

HARD SKILLS

- Code Editor and IDE: Visual Studio Code, Sublime Text, Notepad++, Nano, Vim, Android Studio, NetBeans
- Programming Language: JavaScript, JAVA, PHP
- Database: MySQL, MongoDB
- Markup and Styling: HTML, XML, CSS
- Framework and Library: Laravel, ReactJS, NextJS, ExpressJS, Materializecss
- Tech Stack: MERN, LAMP
- Office Suite: Microsoft Office/Microsoft 365 (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, SharePoint), Adobe Acrobat Reader (PDF)
- Version Control, Terminal, and Operating System: Git, Git Bash, Linux (Ubuntu), Windows PowerShell

SOFT SKILLS

Attractive, talkative, communicative, adaptive, creative, innovative, explorative, observative, cooperative, collaborative, leadership, teamworking, problem solving, critical thinking, time managing, deep learning.